#### Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/surabhi-ms-she-her-2971a1175 (LinkedIn)

## Top Skills

Software Solution Development
Neuro-Linguistic Programming (NLP)
Generative AI Tools

## Languages

English (Professional Working)
Malayalam (Native or Bilingual)

### Certifications

Introduction to Large Language Models

Introduction to Generative Al

# Surabhi MS (she/her)

Chatbot developer | Voice bot | Google Dialog Flow CX | CCAI | Conversational AI | Microsoft Bot Framework | Azure Cognitive Services(QnA) | Google Dialog Flow | Node.js

Thrissur, Kerala, India

# Summary

Hi, my name is Surabhi. With three years of expertise, I am a chatbot developer with voice and chatbot development skills. Microsoft composer, Google dialog flow CX and ES, Microsoft bot framework, CCAI, NLP particularly with Node.js are among my areas of expertise.

# Experience

Miratech

Junior Software Engineer November 2023 - Present (1 year 1 month) Bengaluru, Karnataka, India

Client - Optum UHG

Leading the development of solutions for automation of call center operations, leveraging the Azure Bot Framework for the development of advanced voicebot solutions where the language understanding models are being trained on Azure CLU and IVR automation solutions with Audiocodes.

iNextLabs

System Engineer September 2021 - August 2023 (2 years)

I work as a chatbot developer. I work on Microsoft bots. I have built chatbots using Dialog flow (NLP)

and have worked on Azure Cognitive Services, for example, QnA maker.

Additionally, I have developed mock bot flows.

Mirosi

Digital Marketing Intern
October 2020 - February 2021 (5 months)

Kochi, Kerala, India

I worked with mirosi as a Digital marketing intern for over 3 months. I increased their social following and customer number during this duration. As a computer science student, it was a lovely experience to learn something different, and I'm so happy about it.

## Education

Cochin University of Science and Technology

Master of Computer Applications - MCA, Computer Applications

· (2018 - 2021)

MERCY COLLEGE, PALAKKAD Bachelor's degree, Computer Science